usfinanceresource.com 2012-05-10

# Privacy Policy

Purpose of the Privacy Policy.

USFinancialSource.com is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company web site at www.usfinancialsource.com. We created this Privacy Policy to give you notice of how your private information will be used as a result of submitting it to us. This Policy is only applicable to the Web Site, including any sub-domains, and not to any other web sites that you may be able to access from the Web Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. When you register at USFinancialSource.com, the Personally Identifiable Information you provide to us is used to provide the services you have registered for, to deliver email notifications to you, and from time to time, to validate your identity. Our data collection policies allow you to choose how much information you provide to us, and to control how we use that Personally Identifiable Information as set forth below. To find out more, please read on. 

The purpose of this Policy is to describe the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of the owners of USFinancialSource.com, its parent, subsidiaries and registered d/b/a companies (collectively referred to hereinafter as "Company" or "we" or "us") and all related web sites owned or registered to Company and applies to Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Company on its (a) web sites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Web Site"), (b) on various Third Party web sites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the acquisition of customer information from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party web sites or applications. 

NOTICE CONCERNING CHILDREN. We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user's account. 

Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices.

Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, email address, contact phone number or other information related to of the services you are seeking. We request this information to deliver on the services you are requesting, and to allow us to provide our strongest value to you - a personalized online experience. Information collected online is often defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable: 

  1. Anonymous Information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that thousands of people have visited this Privacy Policy web page, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or their date of birth. What we collect from visits such as this constitutes anonymous information. Some of the individuals who access our services decline to use the personalization features that are available to them, and therefore those individuals are anonymous to us and the only data we collect about them is anonymous information.
  2. Personally Identifiable Information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, email address or phone number. While you can search and browse some sections of our web site without being a registered user, certain activities do require registration. Registering with USFinancialSource.com using the web form will also cause a cookie to be issued; this cookie allows the Company to "recognize" you when you are on our site to allow us to personalize our service for you.

Anonymous Information

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.   
We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 

We may link this automatically-collected data to certain Personally Identifiable Information.   
We may use third-party tracking services that use cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate. 

Personally Identifiable Information

In order to use the basic features of this Web Site, you must register and provide certain personal information. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as your name, email address, mailing address, social security number, drivers license and credit card information, and telephone or cell phone number). You may also provide us with information that, when combined with Personally Identifiable Information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level. We use this information to connect you with the providers of services in which you have expressed interest. Depending on the services you have chosen to use, some or all of your Personally Identifiable Information may be used by USFinancialSource.com to provide such services. Personally Identifiable Information may also be provided to intermediaries and third parties (including affiliates and partners) who assist USFinancialSource.com in providing you with the service upon your request. For example, if you register and desire to get education information, your personally identifiable information may be provided to one or more prospective schools. Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, however, USFinancialSource.com will not rent or sell your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties without your permission. 

USFinancialSource.com is the owner of the information collected on www.usfinancialsource.com. 

Survey Information. Company may collect information from you when you voluntarily complete a Company survey, order form, or a registration page either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties. This method of collection is collectively known as a "Survey." In such Surveys, Company or a third party may ask you to provide personal identifiable information including your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. Company may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from the Web Site. Completing any Survey is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Company or a third party. 

Third Party Information. Company may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and Company subsequently acquires or uses the information provided by the third party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the you may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, Company seeks assurances from the third party that you agreed to provide and have such information acquired by Company. If you did not give express permission, or you would like to remove your permission, you may suppress all of your information by using our convenient [unsubscribe link](http://unsubmyemail.org/MzgxMnwyNA). 

Other Methods of Collecting Personal Information. Other occasions when Company obtains information from you include (1) your claiming a prize or seeking to redeem an offer by Company or by a third party, (2) your requests for assistance through Company's customer service department, and (3) when you voluntarily subscribe to a Company service or newsletter. 

Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Information Collected Using Technology. Company currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, Company may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future. 

(a) Cookies. "Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Web Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this Web Site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on web site usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Web Site. You can disable cookies, although the Web Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of Company's Web Site, you need to accept cookies. Notwithstanding any other provision in this policy, in visiting this site, a third-party advertiser (or its partners) may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. These cookies enable more customized ads, content or services to be provided to you. To trigger these cookies, we may pass an encrypted or 'hashed' (non-human readable) identifier corresponding to your email address to a Web advertising partner, who may place a cookie on your computer. No personally identifiable information is on, or is connected to, these cookies. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.privacychoice.org/companies or http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

(b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Company to track certain web sites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Company also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Company's database. 

(c) IP Addresses. Company automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the Web Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the Web Site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other web sites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those web sites and their pages. 

(d) Computer Profiles. Company may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, Company may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you. 

(e) Data Analysis. Data Analysis technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of Company. 

(f) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, Company strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology. 

No Information Collected from Children. Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 18. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 18, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). 

Credit Card or Bank Information. Company may, in certain instances, collect credit card numbers or banking numbers and related information when an individual places an order from Company. When the credit card information or banking information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Company will use the credit card or banking information for purposes of processing and completing the requested transaction, and the information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. 

Use of Individual Information.

General Use. The following paragraphs describe how Company currently uses Personally Identifiable Information, but Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Company may update this policy from time to time. Company may use Personally Identifiable Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses. 

Email and Unsubscribe Policy. Company uses Personally Identifiable Information to provide other businesses promotional offers by email to individuals. Company may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Company's email lists, please use our [unsubscribe link](http://unsubmyemail.org/MzgxMnwyNA). 

Company's unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by Company on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of Third Parties and your personal information may still be shared with Third Parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends. 

You should also note that unsubscribing from Company's electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the subscriber's information from any Third Party business associates and licensees of the data. Since Third Party associates and licensee partners maintain separate databases from Company, and you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue. 

Content of Email Messages. In certain commercial email messages sent by Company, an Advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Company. The "Subject:" line of Company email messages will usually contain a line provided from the Advertiser to Company. 

Solicited Email. Company only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Web Site to receive email from Company or to individuals who have agreed on a Third Party web site to receive email from Third Parties. As such, Company does not send unsolicited email messages. 

Targeted Advertising. Company may use Personally Identifiable Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Company uses other information to associate an individual with that person's Personally Identifiable Information, and Company attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, and otherwise. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers. 

Telemarketing. Company may use Personally Identifiable Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. You may have your telephone number or cell phone number listed on a state or federal do not call registry. By registering and using this Web Site, You are waiving your rights and privileges under these laws and expressly giving permission of Company and any agent of Company the right to contact you by telephone or cell phone, and you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR § 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time (the "Rule"). Further, if you are residing outside the United States, by registering and using this Web Site, You acknowledge that the processing of your individual information may involve the transfer of such Individual information from within or outside the European Economic Area ("EEA") to countries within or outside the EEA whose data protection regulation may not be as stringent as that within the European Union. We may use individual information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. 

Wireless Addresses. If the e-mail address you provide to Company is a wireless e-mail or text address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Company or its business associates (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. 

Short Message Service. Company may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. Company will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. Company may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies. 

You acknowledge and agree that the SMS Service is provided via wireless systems which use radios (and other means) to transmit communications over complex networks. We do not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. We may also access the content of your account and wireless account with your carrier for the purpose of identifying and resolving technical problems and service-related complaints. 

You may remove your information from Company's database. If you remove your information from Company's database it will no longer be used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. 

Storage of Individual Information. USFinancialSource.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers. Notwithstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered. 

Other Use of Personally Identifiable Information.

Company may also use your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways: 

Third Party Offers. Company will share any and all Personally Identifiable Information with (and may make customer lists available to) companies or other entities not affiliated with the Company that have goods, services and offers that might be of interest to you. Company may, from time to time, provide your Personally Identifiable Information to these entities so that they may send you these offers. 

Marketing. Company will use your Personally Identifiable Information for any marketing and survey purpose on behalf of Company and its affiliates, parent and subsidiaries to send information to you about additional goods or services that may be of interest to you. In addition, Company may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third party agents and independent contractors to help us conduct our marketing and survey efforts and to share with other companies in connection with marketing efforts including but not limited to direct marketing. You may have no relationship with these other companies. 

Co-sponsored Offerings. Company may provide an offering which is co-sponsored by another company. In those situations, the Personally Identifiable Information we obtain from you in connection with such offering may be shared with our co-sponsor. In those situations, our co-sponsors will have the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information for their own purposes, in accordance with their own policies. If you do not wish for the information we obtain from you to be shared with our co-sponsor, then do not enter such contest, sweepstake or other offering or otherwise provide to us any Personally Identifiable Information in connection with such contest, sweepstake or other offering. We are not responsible for how our co-sponsors may use your information. 

Service Providers. We may use third parties to help operate our Web Site and deliver products and services, and may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Web Site or for our business (such as Web Site or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, e-mail service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf). Unless otherwise stated, these companies do not have any right to use the Personally Identifiable Information we provide to them beyond what is necessary for them to assist us. When you conduct e-commerce with one of the e-commerce affiliates or service providers to which the Web Site may be linked, certain Personally Identifiable Information such as your e-mail and home address may be collected by the service provider's server and made available to us. 

Aggregate Statistics. We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Web Site and e-mails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user. 

Complying with Legal Process. Company reserves the right to use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information in response to subpoenas, court orders, warrants, or legal process, or to otherwise establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims or in the event you violate or breach an agreement with Company. Company will use and disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we believe you will harm the property or rights of Company, its owners, or those of Company's other customers. Finally, we will use or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information if we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Company's other policies, or as otherwise required by law when responding to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes. 

Order Fulfillment. Company will transfer your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that you order from such third party while using Company's Web Site or when responding to offers provided by Company. 

Data Summary. Company may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons. 

Third Parties. Company may provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties with whom they have a business relationship for the purposes of securing the services and products you have requested or provide you with additional marketing materials from which you may choose additional products or services. 

Business Transitions. In the event Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets as well as in the event of a bankruptcy, assignment for benefit of creditors or receivership, your Personally Identifiable Information may be disclosed and will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. Company further reserves the right to disclose, transfer or sell your personal information to companies who are affiliated with Company in Company's sole discretion. 

Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the web sites and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you. 

Links. The Company's Web Site and email messages may sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

Foreign use of the Website.

To the extent that you are accessing the Web Site while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Personally Identifiable Information you are providing Company is collected and stored in the United States and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States. 

California User Consumer Rights.

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov). For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/)

If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at USFinancialSource.com, 3435 Ocean Park Blvd., Suite 107-282, Santa Monica, CA 90405, U.S.A. 

Changes in this Privacy Statement. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page.
